var Questions = {
  1: {
    question: 'Is it living thing or non-living thing?',
    options: [
      { answer: 'Living Thing', next: 2 },
      { answer: 'Non-living Thing', next: 3 },
    ],
    prev: 0,
  },
  2: {
    question: 'Human or non-human?',
    options: [
      { answer: 'Human', next: 26 },
      { answer: 'Non-human', next: 7 },
    ],
    prev: 1,
  },
  3: {
    question: 'Non-living thing',
    options: [
      { answer: 'Wand', next: 4 },
      { answer: 'Sword', next: 5 },
      { answer: 'Onsen (Hot Spring)', next: 6 },
    ],
    prev: 1,
  },
  4: {
    question: 'Wand',
    options: [{ manga: 111846 }],
    prev: 3,
  },
  5: {
    question: 'Sword',
    options: [{ manga: 103144 }],
    prev: 3,
  },
  6: {
    question: 'Onsen (Hot Spring)',
    options: [{ manga: 107893 }],
    prev: 3,
  },
  7: {
    question: 'Humanoid shape?',
    options: [
      { answer: 'Yes', next: 8 },
      { answer: 'No', next: 20 },
    ],
    prev: 2,
  },
  8: {
    question: 'Humanoid',
    options: [
      { answer: 'Angel', next: 9 },
      { answer: 'Demon', next: 10 },
      { answer: 'Orc(?)', next: 11 },
      { answer: 'Dragon', next: 12 },
      { answer: 'God', next: 13 },
      { answer: 'Dark Elf Vampire', next: 14 },
      { answer: 'Incubus/Succubus', next: 15 },
      { answer: 'Bear', next: 16 },
      { answer: 'Skeleton', next: 17 },
      { answer: 'Undead', next: 18 },
      { answer: 'Vampire', next: 19 },
    ],
    prev: 7,
  },
  9: {
    question: 'Angel',
    options: [{ manga: 108598 }],
    prev: 8,
  },
  10: {
    question: 'Demon',
    options: [{ manga: 91714 }, { manga: 115200 }],
    prev: 8,
  },
  11: {
    question: 'Desk Orc',
    options: [{ manga: 127075 }],
    prev: 8,
  },
  12: {
    question: 'Dragon',
    options: [{ manga: 100923 }],
    prev: 8,
  },
  13: {
    question: 'God',
    options: [{ manga: 129759 }, { manga: 117595 }],
    prev: 8,
  },
  14: {
    question: 'Half Dark Elf, Half Vampire',
    options: [{ manga: 114849 }],
    prev: 8,
  },
  15: {
    question: 'Incubus/Succubus',
    options: [{ manga: 98156 }, { manga: 113999 }],
    prev: 8,
  },
  16: {
    question: 'Bear',
    options: [{ manga: 109770 }],
    prev: 8,
  },
  17: {
    question: 'Skeleton',
    options: [{ manga: 105328 }],
    prev: 8,
  },
  18: {
    question: 'Undead',
    options: [{ manga: 81667 }],
    prev: 8,
  },
  19: {
    question: 'Vampire',
    options: [{ manga: 107138 }],
    prev: 8,
  },
  20: {
    question: 'Non-humanoid',
    options: [
      { answer: 'Behemoth', next: 21 },
      { answer: 'Dragon', next: 22 },
      { answer: 'Fenrir (Wolf)', next: 23 },
      { answer: 'Slime', next: 24 },
      { answer: 'Spider', next: 25 },
    ],
    prev: 7,
  },
  21: {
    question: 'Behemoth',
    options: [{ manga: 113194 }],
    prev: 20,
  },
  22: {
    question: 'Dragon',
    options: [{ manga: 113178 }],
    prev: 20,
  },
  23: {
    question: 'Fenrir (Wolf)',
    options: [{ manga: 113081 }],
    prev: 20,
  },
  24: {
    question: 'Slime',
    options: [{ manga: 87609 }],
    prev: 20,
  },
  25: {
    question: 'Spider',
    options: [{ manga: 95353 }],
    prev: 20,
  },
  26: {
    question: 'Anti-hero?',
    options: [
      { answer: 'Yes', next: 27 },
      { answer: 'No', next: 37 },
    ],
    prev: 2,
  },
  27: {
    question: 'Job/Role?',
    options: [
      { answer: 'Adventurer', next: 28 },
      { answer: 'Assassin', next: 29 },
      { answer: 'Commander', next: 30 },
      { answer: 'Hero', next: 31 },
      { answer: 'Hunter', next: 32 },
      { answer: 'Magician', next: 33 },
      { answer: 'Slave Master', next: 34 },
      { answer: 'Student', next: 35 },
      { answer: 'Warrior', next: 36 },
      { answer: 'Gladiator', next: 62 },
    ],
    prev: 26,
  },
  28: {
    question: 'Adventurer',
    options: [{ manga: 96528 }, { manga: 82399 }],
    prev: 27,
  },
  29: {
    question: 'Assassin',
    options: [{ manga: 119022 }, { manga: 117886 }],
    prev: 27,
  },
  30: {
    question: 'Commander',
    options: [{ manga: 98436 }],
    prev: 27,
  },
  31: {
    question: 'Hero',
    options: [{ manga: 122650 }, { manga: 108197 }, { manga: 116772 }, { manga: 105029 }, { manga: 67615 }],
    prev: 27,
  },
  32: {
    question: 'Hunter',
    options: [{ manga: 98820 }],
    prev: 27,
  },
  33: {
    question: 'Magician',
    options: [{ manga: 114595 }],
    prev: 27,
  },
  34: {
    question: 'Slave Master',
    options: [{ manga: 109649 }],
    prev: 27,
  },
  35: {
    question: 'Student',
    options: [{ manga: 131228 }],
    prev: 27,
  },
  36: {
    question: 'Warrior',
    options: [{ manga: 13801 }],
    prev: 27,
  },
  37: {
    question: 'Job/Role?',
    options: [
      { answer: 'Unknown', next: 38 },
      { answer: 'Adventurer', next: 39 },
      { answer: 'Alchemist', next: 40 },
      { answer: 'Aristocrat', next: 63 },
      { answer: 'Assassin', next: 41 },
      { answer: 'Butler', next: 42 },
      { answer: 'Cafe Owner', next: 43 },
      { answer: 'Cook', next: 44 },
      { answer: 'Dungeon Master', next: 45 },
      { answer: 'Employee', next: 46 },
      { answer: 'Farmer', next: 47 },
      { answer: 'Hero', next: 48 },
      { answer: 'King', next: 49 },
      { answer: 'Knight', next: 50 },
      { answer: 'Magician', next: 51 },
      { answer: 'Merchant', next: 52 },
      { answer: 'Prince', next: 53 },
      { answer: 'Secretary', next: 54 },
      { answer: 'Slave', next: 55 },
      { answer: 'Student', next: 56 },
      { answer: 'Summoner', next: 57 },
      { answer: 'Swordman', next: 58 },
      { answer: 'Witch', next: 59 },
      { answer: 'Wrestle', next: 60 },
      { answer: 'Tamer', next: 61 },
    ],
    prev: 26,
  },
  38: {
    question: 'Unknown',
    options: [{ manga: 124543 }, { manga: 112684 }],
    prev: 37,
  },
  39: {
    question: 'Adventurer',
    options: [
      { manga: 130204 },
      { manga: 115156 },
      { manga: 119156 },
      { manga: 113752 },
      { manga: 115978 },
      { manga: 111287 },
      { manga: 113716 },
      { manga: 91656 },
      { manga: 119625 },
      { manga: 122775 },
      { manga: 80385 },
      { manga: 106608 },
      { manga: 83021 },
      { manga: 119152 },
      { manga: 70259 },
      { manga: 90117 },
      { manga: 114568 },
      { manga: 121083 },
      { manga: 122265 },
    ],
    prev: 37,
  },
  40: {
    question: 'Alchemist',
    options: [{ manga: 106300 }],
    prev: 37,
  },
  41: {
    question: 'Assassin',
    options: [{ manga: 115067 }],
    prev: 37,
  },
  42: {
    question: 'Butler',
    options: [{ manga: 6778 }],
    prev: 37,
  },
  43: {
    question: 'Cafe Owner',
    options: [{ manga: 125904 }],
    prev: 37,
  },
  44: {
    question: 'Cook',
    options: [{ manga: 105747 }, { manga: 119098 }, { manga: 110081 }],
    prev: 37,
  },
  45: {
    question: 'Dungeon Master',
    options: [{ manga: 89161 }],
    prev: 37,
  },
  46: {
    question: 'Employee',
    options: [{ manga: 124995 }],
    prev: 37,
  },
  47: {
    question: 'Farmer',
    options: [{ manga: 110460 }],
    prev: 37,
  },
  48: {
    question: 'Hero',
    options: [
      { manga: 106810 },
      { manga: 123093 },
      { manga: 115310 },
      { manga: 124797 },
      { manga: 66685 },
      { manga: 123067 },
      { manga: 134764 },
      { manga: 109931 },
    ],
    prev: 37,
  },
  49: {
    question: 'King',
    options: [{ manga: 48397 }],
    prev: 37,
  },
  50: {
    question: 'Knight',
    options: [{ manga: 74695 }],
    prev: 37,
  },
  51: {
    question: 'Magician',
    options: [{ manga: 86043 }, { manga: 103364 }, { manga: 74701 }],
    prev: 37,
  },
  52: {
    question: 'Merchant',
    options: [{ manga: 125498 }, { manga: 113152 }, { manga: 147137 }],
    prev: 37,
  },
  53: {
    question: 'Prince',
    options: [{ manga: 104322 }],
    prev: 37,
  },
  54: {
    question: 'Secretary',
    options: [{ manga: 107110 }],
    prev: 37,
  },
  55: {
    question: 'Slave',
    options: [{ manga: 129229 }, { manga: 133078 }, { manga: 80187 }],
    prev: 37,
  },
  56: {
    question: 'Student',
    options: [{ manga: 99313 }, { manga: 99377 }, { manga: 104241 }, { manga: 106788 }, { manga: 49331 }, { manga: 131255 }],
    prev: 37,
  },
  57: {
    question: 'Summoner',
    options: [{ manga: 100377 }, { manga: 136309 }],
    prev: 37,
  },
  58: {
    question: 'Swordman',
    options: [{ manga: 116167 }],
    prev: 37,
  },
  59: {
    question: 'Witch',
    options: [{ manga: 110288 }, { manga: 146368 }],
    prev: 37,
  },
  60: {
    question: 'Wrestle',
    options: [{ manga: 107261 }],
    prev: 37,
  },
  61: {
    question: 'Tamer',
    options: [{ manga: 115917 }],
    prev: 37,
  },
  62: {
    question: 'Gladiator',
    options: [{ manga: 152415 }],
    prev: 27,
  },
  63: {
    question: 'Aristocrat',
    options: [{ manga: 127781 }],
    prev: 37,
  },
};
